stakeholdermap.com 2019-01-17

# 

                                        Privacy Policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out
how we will treat your personal information.
(1)     What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a)     information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website
        (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source,
        length of visit and number of page views);
(b)     information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in
        relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make
        of our goods or services (including your name, address and email address);
(d)     information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website
        services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including name and email
        address);
(e)     any other information that you choose to send to us/
(2)     Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by
the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser
requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the
web browser.
We use “session” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track
of you whilst you navigate the website.
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates
statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are
stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to
create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's
privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.
We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are
tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will
track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest
categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager,
available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense
partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this
opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your
opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a
particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at:
http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject
just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by

clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the
sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the
usability of many websites[, including this one.
(3)     Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this
privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a)     administer the website;
(b)     improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
(c)     enable your use of the services available on the website;
(d)     send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services
        purchased via the website;
(e)     send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(f)     send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(g)     send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(h)     send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our
        business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may
        be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by
        email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer
        require marketing communications);]
(i)     provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this
        information will not be used to identify any individual user;
(j)     deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;
        and
[(k)    OTHER USES.
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish
and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third
parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider,
Paypal. You should only provide your personal information to Paypal after reviewing the
Paypal privacy policy (available at www.paypal.com). We will share information with
Paypal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make
via our website.
(4)     Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to[any of our employees, officers, agents,
suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out
in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you:
(a)     to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)     in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)     in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing
        information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit
        risk); and
(d)     to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we
        are (or are contemplating) selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third
parties.
(5)    International data transfers
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any
of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in
accordance with this privacy policy.
Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United
States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the
European Economic Areas (EEA).
In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be
published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.
You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.
(6)    Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss,
misuse or alteration of your personal information.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot
guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
(7)    Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our
website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any
changes.
[We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
(8)    Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.
Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at
£10.00).
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email
at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of
your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to

opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)
(9)     Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy
policies or practices of third party websites.
(10)    Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be
corrected or updated.
(11)    Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal
data, please write to us by email to tamzin@stakeholdermap.com.
(12)    Data controller
The data controller responsible for our website is T Morphy.
                                 This privacy policy is courtesy of
                         Employment Law Contracts and Website Law
